Now, gimaro, I ask the council's permission.
Three, two, one.
Yay.
Today we will both be chairleaders.
I'm excited.
Thank you very much.
I'm nervous.
Unfortunately, it's raining, but I'm a woman of the rain, so I can't say, "Please let it be sunny.
The moment I say it, it's pouring.
You really are a rain woman.
It rained on all my school trips, too.
Nobody comes to see the show?
There is no one here.
Zero spectators today?
Zero spectators?
Is that possible?
Can't they get in yet?
It stopped raining.
I'm sure of it.
I just noticed.
It's just the beginning. From now on.
It will clear up.
Please.
Anpanman.
I said the strongest and happiest Anpanman.
The Strongest Happy Carnival
I said Anpanman.
Wrap me around your live mosh and give me a kiss, please.
Anpanman
Thank you.
I did Hansa.
I did.
I did it.
Please don't use it.
Please don't use it. It's like I bullied you.
The opening.
Miho Mizutani!
There is one more kind.
Amazing. I mean, one name here, two names here, three names here, four names here, five names here, and six names here.
That's amazing, six names.
And there are color contacts in there. Here.
Yes! That's all.
That's all.
Good morning!
I brought him back.
Radio.
We still don't know what we're going to do.
Yeah!
Yay!
The Rajbasi Brothers are here! The Rajbasi Eagles!
Please join us in the audience and everyone watching on YouTube to dance with us!
I like you, Piqui!
Funny!
Piqui, you're right!
I'll get you, I'll get you.
Let it flow! Hey!
Even though I've fallen a million times.
I won't give up.
More, more, more
Don't just go for the high ground
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on!
Go!
Go home!
More!
Shine!
Everybody!
Gate Club camera!
I'm off!
Growing up, I wonder if we're all connected in our own way.
I'm lost, I'm lost, I'm lost, I'm lost, I'm lost, I'm lost...
All of it, all of it, maximum happiness.
Let's hit it!
Let's let the best high choo-choo roll loose
Let's kiss!
My heart won't die
Even if it's clinging to you!
You're walking too fast.
Good luck.
Keep practicing.
Are you okay? Will it change? Here.
Thank you very much.
Good luck.
What if I get nervous?
If you get nervous, everyone is rooting for you.
They're cheering for me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Go for it!
I'm going to cry.
I feel like I'm crying all by myself.
Oh no, I'm going to cry.
Here you go.
Why isn't it today, since I got the front?
How do you not get nervous?
Where are you coming from?
Come to the office.
Come to my office.Come to my office.
Oh, it hurts.
Ouch.
Well, I'll let you get it anyway.
I'll scare him a little.
I'll scare him.
Wait, that's not good.
It's not good.
The world of the ball.
Oh, no.
Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Today's article is about
you both have enjoyed over the past two years.
We send you a very big round of applause.
It's been called the article of forever.
Congratulations, and thank you for your interest.
Once again, we are not interested in
Please return the favor.
Thank you very much.
Yes, cheese.
I'll go one more.
Thank you very much.
Here we go.
Yes, cheese!
OK.
Finally, it's over.
I'm shaking all over and I don't know what's going on.
I don't know what to do.
I want to get it going.
I'll go. I'll do my best.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Yuka from the first three years.
From here on out, let's support our creation.
Let's all raise our music and get excited!
Let's start the music!
Here we go.
Yes, I'm going.
Three, two, one. Here we go.
What happened to the Raphs in the 2nd inning?
What's the Rakuten Eagles' offense in the bottom of the 3rd?
Number 7 DH, number 33, Ginji!
OK! That's great!
What about the attack of Raffeins in the 2nd inning?
Here we go!
Come on, boy!
That's great! I'm really going for it!
Let's go for it!
Tokyo Metropolitan Transportation Bureau Type 8800 Train
Thank you for watching.
Aww.
Wow.
I shouldn't be too convinced.
It's the other way around.
It's easier to see it the other way around.
Yes, it is.
Oh, too bad I couldn't move.
Sad.
I used to be able to move around a lot.
It's hard to get this seat.
Don't you want to take a picture of this?
You never know.
I'm an incredibly happy person.
There it is, there it is.
Good memories.
Thank you very much.
See you next time.
I'll do my best!
Original.
Anything original is fine.
In all directions.
I'm going to take three more pictures, so please move.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Yeah!
Three, two, one.
Second one, three, two, one.
Last one!
Three, two, one.
Yes, thank you!
Thank you very much!
Please subscribe to our channel.